{"data":[{"question":"I can't describe people as well as you could.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"describe","b":"people","c":"as well as","d":"could","answer":"4","explain":"- Could-> can","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I was scared to tell him what me really thought.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was scared","b":"to tell","c":"me","d":"really","answer":"3","explain":"- Me-> I","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"There are about 3,000 living languages in the world today, but only about six of them are major language of the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"living languages","c":"six of them","d":"language","answer":"4","explain":"- Language-> langueges","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Jack has become confidently as a result of his success.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has become","b":"confidently","c":"as","d":"his success","answer":"2","explain":"- Confidently-> confident","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"He didn't given any reason for his strange behavior that day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"didn't given","b":"any reason","c":"strange","d":"that day","answer":"1","explain":"- Didn't given-> didn't give","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I had lost his phone number so I couldn't to contact him before.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had lost","b":"so","c":"to contact","d":"before","answer":"3","explain":"- To contact-> contact","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A lot of things keep stopping me for walking.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A lot of","b":"stopping","c":"for","d":"walking","answer":"3","explain":"- For-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"She couldn't believe that she has finally found her brother.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"believe","b":"that","c":"has","d":"finally","answer":"3","explain":"- Has-> had","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The invention of the transistor on 1948 brought about a revolution in computer development.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"invention","b":"on","c":"about","d":"computer","answer":"2","explain":"-On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Some improvement have recently been made in the bus service in this town.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"improvement","b":"recently","c":"been","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"-Improvement-> improvements","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}